{"data":[{"question":"She did not want to go back to the shops because it was very lately.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"did not","b":"to go","c":"because","d":"lately","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Lately-> late","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The last time I went to London, I didn't have time to visit all the place I wanted to see.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"time","b":"to","c":"didn't","d":"place","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Place->places","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I soon got to know where were the main streets.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"got","b":"where","c":"were","d":"streets","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n-  were the main streets-> the main streets were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I can spend quite a long time in Westminster Abbey and learn of all the interesting things there.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"quite","b":"in","c":"of","d":"there","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Of-> about","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"They are very pleasant to travel by steamer down the Thames from Westminster to Tower Bridge.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"They are","b":"pleasant","c":"by","d":"down","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- They are-> it's","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"One day a fame singer was invited by a rich lady to her house.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"One day","b":"fame","c":"was","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Fame-> famous","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"At ten o'clock, the singer was asked coming upstairs to the lady's guests.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was asked","b":"coming","c":"upstairs","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Coming-> to come","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"William H.Harrison, the man who served the most short term, died of pneumonia several weeks after his inauguration.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"who","b":"the most short","c":"of","d":"after","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- The most short-> the shortest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Abraham Lincoln was one of four presidents who was assassinated.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"one","b":"presidents","c":"who","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"James A. Garfield was shot during his first year in office by a man to that he wouldn't give a job.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"shot","b":"during","c":"that","d":"wouldn't","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- That-> whom","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}